欢迎光临介绍第1图像处理。
Welcome to Section 1 of Introduction to Image Processing.
本节提供的典型的图像处理任务的概述
This section provides an overview of typical image processing tasks
并且将在本课程主题的一些例子。
and some examples of topics that are covered in this course.
在几乎任何图像处理任务的第一个步骤
The first step in almost any image processing task
越来越的图像转换成计算机
is getting the images into the computer
或导入图像
or importing the images
成将用于处理软件。
into the software that will be used for the processing.
这样做的一种方式
One way of doing that
是由计算机和软件连接到一个摄像头。
is by connecting the computer and the software to a camera.
这显示了CurrentImage功能
This shows the CurrentImage function
在Wolfram语言，
in the Wolfram Language,
从相机拍摄图像
which captures an image from a camera
连接到该计算机
connected to this computer
进口图像到这个Wolfram语言系统。
and imports the image into this Wolfram Language system.
您也可以导入图片
You can also import images
从您的计算机上或从互联网上的文件。
from files on your computer or from the internet.
例如，该进口JPEG图像
For example, this imports a JPEG image
从互联网上的文件。
from a file on the internet.
JPEG是几十种常见的图像格式之一。
JPEG is one of dozens of common image formats.
图像也可以在计算机内产生的。
Images can also be generated within the computer.
例如，该使用图像功能
For example, this uses the Image function
从数字的表中创建的图像。
to create an image from a table of numbers.
图像也可以创建
Images can also be created
从东西显示在计算机屏幕上。
from things displayed on the computer screen.
例如，该显示的图
For example, this displays a plot
然后使用光栅化功能
and then uses the Rasterize function
该显示转换为图像。
to convert that display to an image.
然后，图像可以被编辑或修改像任何其他图像。
The image can then be edited or modified like any other image.
之后的图像已导入，
After an image has been imported,
有各种各样的事情
there is a variety of things
可以做来修改图像，
that can be done to modify the image,
无论是审美的原因
either for aesthetic reasons
或以制备出图像用于进一步分析。
or to prepare the image for further analysis.
例如，这显示了一个操纵结果
For example, this shows a Manipulate result
与用于修改控制
with controls for modifying
亮度和对比度的图像。
the brightness and contrast in an image.
操作调节亮度和对比度
Operations for adjusting brightness and contrast
在第2和3进行讨论。
are discussed in Sections 2 and 3.
对比度和亮度调节
Contrast and brightness adjustment
通过改变图像直方图工作，
work by changing the image histogram,
这是颜色的分布
which is the distribution of colors
和图像中的强度。
and intensities in an image.
有几种常见的操作
There are several common operations
涉及图像直方图的其他修改。
that involve other modifications of the image histogram.
例如，这显示了一个操作
For example, this shows an operation
称为颜色转移或直方图匹配
called color transfer or histogram matching,
其改变的颜色的分布在一个图像
which modifies the distribution of colors in one image
匹配的颜色在另一图像上的分布。
to match the distribution of colors in another image.
直方图匹配和一些相关的操作
Histogram matching and some related operations
在第4节中讨论。
are discussed in Section 4.
另一组基本的图像操作
Another group of basic image operations
是像裁剪和旋转的几何操作
is geometric operations like cropping and rotating
并调整图像。
and resizing the image.
例如，该节目
For example, this shows
样本图像的裁剪和旋转版本
a cropped and rotated version of the sample image
使用ImageRotate和ImageTrim功能创建的。
created using the ImageRotate and ImageTrim functions.
这里是一个操纵结果
Here is a Manipulate result
这显示了这些几何操作
that shows these geometric operations
带滑块控制剪切的量
with sliders to control the amount of cropping
和调整大小和旋转。
and resizing and rotating.
基本的几何运算将在第8。
Basic geometric operations are covered in Section 8.
在许多图像处理任务的一个关键步骤
A key step in many image processing tasks
是分割，
is segmentation,
这意味着分离出图像的不同部分。
which means separating out different parts of the image.
有分割的方法很多。
There are many methods of segmentation.
这说明分割用二值化的功能，
This shows segmentation using the Binarize function,
该图像分离成两个区段
which separates the image into two segments
基于亮度。
based on brightness.
从分割结果在这里代表
The result from segmentation is represented here
by a black-and-white image,
与由该搜索结果的白色部分中确定的明亮的段
with the bright segment identified by the white parts of that result
和较暗的段确定了黑色部分。
and the darker segment identified by the black parts.
一旦图像被分割，
Once the image has been segmented,
有可以用它做很多事情。
there are many things that can be done with it.
例如，该挑选出的最大的连接分量
For example, this picks out the biggest connected components
在分割，
in that segmentation,
在该示例中是比萨饼的切片。
which in this example are the slices of the pizza.
此输入使用ComponentMeasurements功能
This input uses the ComponentMeasurements function
算在分割比萨饼的件数
to count the number of pieces of pizza in that segmentation
并给每一块的大小。
and give the size of each piece.
分割的一般话题
The general topic of segmentation
具体分割使用二值化功能
and specifically segmentation using the Binarize function
将在第5。
are covered in Section 5.
这也是值得注意的是，这些最后两个输入
It is also worth noting that those last two inputs
示出的图像处理的区域
illustrate an area of image processing
所谓的图像分析，
called image analysis,
其目的是从图像获取信息
where the goal is to get information from the image
而不是仅仅修改图像来获得另一幅图像。
instead of just modifying the image to get another image.
有分割的许多其他方法。
There are many other methods of segmentation.
一种方法是聚类，这可以，例如，
One method is clustering, which can, for example,
段由图像中的编组相似的颜色的图像。
segment an image by grouping similar colors in an image.
这说明细分的集群
This shows segmentation by clustering
用于将样本图像分离成五个段。
used to separate the sample image into five segments.
彩色化功能在这里使用
The Colorize function is used here
显示以对比色每个段。
to display each segment in a contrasting color.
分割的另一种方法是分水岭分割。
Another method of segmentation is watershed segmentation.
作为一个例子，这个输入显示一个分水岭算法
As an example, this input shows a watershed algorithm
用于卫星图像分离
used to separate a satellite image
成在河边的相对侧上的部件。
into components on opposite sides of a river.
分割通过聚类在第7节中描述了
Segmentation by clustering is described in Section 7,
和分割的其它方法在第11部分中描述。
and other methods of segmentation are described in Section 11.
之一中使用的图像段的是作为掩模
One use of an image segment is as a mask
提供一种方式做事对图像的选定部分。
to provide a way to do things to selected parts of an image.
例如，这示出了分割
For example, this shows a segmentation
从一切比萨分离图像中，
that separates the pizza from everything else in the image,
这使用了链段作为掩模
and this uses that segment as a mask
从一切去除颜色
to remove color from everything
除图像的掩盖部以外。
other than the masked part of the image.
所以背景变成了黑色和白色
So the background becomes black and white
和比萨饼是彩色。
and the pizza remains in color.
有迹象表明，可以用颜色做很多其他的事情。
There are many other things that can be done with color.
下面是使用ColorDistance功能的输入
Here is an input that uses the ColorDistance function
细分基于相似于绿色的形象，
to segment the image based on similarity to the color green,
标识上的比萨饼绿色的东西。
which identifies the green things on the pizza.
这些操作和一些基本的色彩理论
These operations and some basic color theory
在第6节中讨论。
are discussed in Section 6.
图像处理的另一个广泛的领域
Another broad area of image processing
是图像增强，
is image enhancement,
其包括工具在图像中的噪声降低
which includes tools for reducing noise in images
并且在图像缺陷修复。
and for repairing defects in images.
例如，下面是样本图像的噪声版本，
For example, here is a noisy version of the sample image,
而这种输入显示理顺噪声
And this input shows smoothing out the noise
使用高斯滤波器。
using a Gaussian filter.
有降噪的许多其他方法。
There are many other methods of noise reduction.
这示出了方法调用的平均移滤波器
This shows a method called a mean shift filter
这确实去除噪声的稍微好一点的工作
that does a slightly better job of removing the noise
同时保留在图像中尖锐的边缘。
while preserving sharp edges in the image.
图像缺陷常常可以校正
Image defects can often be corrected
使用称为修补方法，
using a method called inpainting,
其使用颜色和纹理通过填充工作在缺陷
which works by filling in defects using colors and textures
从图像的周边部分。
from the surrounding parts of the image.
对于补绘，图像的一部分
For inpainting, the part of the image
即在通过掩模鉴定填补。
that is to be filled in is identified by a mask.
由此可见修补用掩模使用
This shows inpainting used with a mask
该标识的一切比其他披萨
that identifies everything other than the pizza
作为图像的部分将被填充，
as the part of the image that is to be filled in,
这基本上消除了背景。
which basically removes the background.
有了一些调整，
With a few adjustments,
背景也可以用更多的比萨饼填充。
the background can also be filled in with more pizza.
工具用于降低噪声和其它图像增强
Tools for noise reduction and other image enhancements
在第9节中讨论。
are discussed in Section 9.
第10节讲述特征检测的一般话题。
Section 10 covers the general topic of feature detection.
在许多应用中，识别是非常重要的
In many applications, it is important to identify
状的线和边缘的图像的基本特征。
basic features of an image like lines and edges.
例如，这显示了ImageLines起作用
For example, this shows the ImageLines function
用于检测图像中的行。
used to detect lines in an image.
在这个例子中，这些线路可以是有用
In this example, those lines could be useful
后续操作
for subsequent operations
如去除透视畸变。
such as removing perspective distortion.
根据不同的应用，
Depending on the application,
几乎在图像上任何事情都可能是一个特征。
almost anything on an image could be a feature.
例如，该使用ImageKeypoints功能
For example, this uses the ImageKeypoints function
识别某一类
to identify a certain class
的图像中的潜在的有趣的功能。
of potentially interesting features in an image.
这些功能可以在各种应用中重要的是，
Those features could be important in a variety of applications,
如，例如，
such as, for example,
修剪基于特征的位置的图像。
trimming the image based on the locations of features.
第12节描述了不同类业务
Section 12 describes a diverse class of operations
从数学形态学使用的想法，
that use ideas from mathematical morphology,
这通常意味着这些操作工作
which typically means that these operations work
考虑关系
by considering relationships
的图像中的相邻的位置之间。
between neighboring locations in an image.
例如，这显示了一个形态运算
For example, this shows a morphological operation
called a top-hat transform,
用于除去大的特征
used to remove the large features
和在背景阴影的变化
and the variation in background shading
从图像。
from an image.
其结果是，强调图像
The result is an image that emphasizes
精细度的原始图像。
the finer details of the original image.
这显示了另一种形态操作
This shows another morphological operation
所谓测地扩张，
called geodesic dilation,
其在这里使用通过电路来重建两个路径
which is used here to reconstruct two paths through a circuit
基于标记图像即识别开始点上
based on a marker image that identifies starting points
关于这两个路径。
on those two paths.
新开发的一个特别活跃的区域
A particularly active area of new development
在图像处理中是机器学习的应用，
in image processing is application of machine learning,
其上覆盖第13节。
which is covered in Section 13.
例如，这显示了FindFaces起作用，
For example, this shows the FindFaces function,
它采用了机器学习算法
which uses a machine learning algorithm
找到图像中的人脸。
to find human faces in an image.
下面是另一个例子。
Here is another example.
这显示了ImageIdentify功能，
This shows the ImageIdentify function,
它采用了机器学习算法
which uses a machine learning algorithm
经过训练，以识别图像中的主要对象。
that has been trained to identify the main object in an image.
此外
In addition to
these built-in functions,
有一个庞大且不断增长的收集功能
there is a large and growing collection of functions
在钨神经网络库。
in the Wolfram Neural Net Repository.
神经网络是在机器学习中使用的常用方法。
Neural nets are a common method used in machine learning.
部13包括几个例子
Section 13 includes several examples
从神经网络库。
from the Neural Net Repository.
最后一节，第14节，是一组实施例
The final section, Section 14, is a set of examples
选择来说明
chosen to illustrate
这些技术是如何覆盖在前面的章节
how the techniques covered in earlier sections
可以在完整的应用程序中使用。
can be used in complete applications.
这说明一个抖动的视频稳定，
This shows stabilization of a shaky video,
这是在第14的实施例之一。
which is one of the examples in Section 14.
That’s the end of the examples
本节。
for this section.
下面是本课程大纲，
Here is the outline for this course,
其被设计成使用实际的例子
which is designed to use practical examples
提供了基础
to provide a foundation
为解决图像处理问题。
for solving problems in image processing.